

Daniel Siedlecki Developer

SKILLS

Programming:

HTML, SCSS, JavaScript/TypeScript

Node.js (Express, socket.io, passport)

Vue.js

React.js

C#

APEX, LWC

Python

Technologies:

REST

Databases:

SQL, SOQL, MongoDB

Administration:

Microsoft Excel, Windows Server, Salesforce Administration, Azure

Graphics:

Figma, Adobe Photoshop

Languages:

Polish - Native

English - Inter-mediate

Other:

Git, Jira, Postman, Driver's License B

SOFT

- teamwork
- quick learning abillity
- organizational skills

REALIZATIONS

I showcase my projects on my website: www.daniel-siedlecki.pl and my GitHub

+48 534 166 602

in Linkedin

mrSiedlecki@outlook.com

daniel-siedlecki.pl

Github

My Trailhead

PERSONAL

I am a beginner developer. I am passionate hardworking and knowledge driven person. Even though I don't have extensive commercial experience, I always strive to find a solution to every problem. My interests are powerlifting, strength training and Computer Graphics.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER NETWORK ENGINEERING

WSB Meritum University

10.2020 - Ongoing

(Fulltime Studies)

EXPERIENCE

Junior Salesforce Developer 08.2023 - Ongoing Karpato

Completed Salesforce 365 Bootcamp

Responsibilites: Creating custom Fullstack solutions in LWC, Apex and Visualforce languages.

Frontend Web Developer

02.2023 - 07.2023

Zeto - Świdnica Sp. z o.o.

Responsibilites: Participation in a web application project at Portiernia. My main tasks were designing the entire Front End for this web application using the Vue framework

CERTIFICATIONS

- Altkom Acadamy Training in GIT Agile and Modern Code Repository
- SAP University Alliances Integrated Information System SAP S/4HANA
- Microsoft Azure Fundamentals